styletread.com.au 2019-03-05

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy 

Styletread values your privacy and takes great care protecting the information you provide us.

Collection of Personal Information

When you create a Styletread account, the personal information we collect may include your:

  1. Name
  2. Delivery Address
  3. Email Address
  4. Telephone Number
  5. Mobile Number
  6. Date of Birth
  7. Gender

The personal information we collect from you will be used in some or all of the following ways:

  1. To deliver the products you have purchased via the Styletread website
  2. To communicate with you during the delivery process of the product and for customer support purposes
  3. To provide you with relevant product information
  4. To aid Styletread in the development of new products and services
  5. To optimise the site and your shopping experience

Customer Communications

Styletread will communicate with you about your order and the purchased product using email and by phone. Account holders must provide a valid email address to Styletread for this purpose.

Styletread may also request feedback on your order, the shopping experience and the products offered via emails and surveys for the purpose of improving Styletread’s service and product offering. If you do not wish to receive such material, you may unsubscribe from our mailing list at any time by emailing [service@styletread.com.au](mailto:service@styletread.com.au).

When you select to be a Styletread subscriber, we'll also use your personal information to send you marketing or promotional information from time to time. You can opt out of receiving marketing information from Styletread at any time by using the unsubscribe function within the email newsletter or by changing the settings under your [My Account](https://www.styletread.com.au/customer/account/ "My Account on Styletread") section.

Updating Your Personal Information

You can update your personal information by accessing your account by logging in to [My Account](https://www.styletread.com.au/customer/account/ "My Account on Styletread").  You can also access this page in the navigation on the top right of the [Styletread](https://www.styletread.com.au/customer/account/ "Styletread") website. Use your email address and password to login and update your account details.

Security of Your Personal Information

We assure you that all information we collect will be safely and securely stored.

We protect your personal information by:

  1. Restricting access to personal information
  2. Maintaining technology products to prevent unauthorised computer access
  3. Securely destroying your personal information when it's no longer needed for our record retention purposes

When purchasing from Styletread, your financial details are passed through a secure server using the latest 128-bit SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption technology. 128-bit SSL encryption is approximated to take at least one trillion years to break, and is the industry standard. If you have any questions regarding our security policy, please contact the Customer Happiness team on [service@styletread.com.au](mailto:service@styletread.com.au).

Disclosure of Personal Information

We value our customers and will not share your information with any other organisations other than related companies and those third parties directly related to the delivery of the products you have purchased from the Styletread website.

There may be some exceptional circumstances for disclosing your personal information, such as when there are grounds to believe that the disclosure is necessary to prevent a threat to life or health, or for law enforcement purposes.

Styletread is committed to complying with the Privacy Act and the National Privacy principles.

Complaints About Breaches of Privacy

If you believe that your privacy has been breached by Styletread, you can contact the Customer Happiness team on [service@styletread.com.au](mailto:service@styletread.com.au) and all attempts will be made to resolve the matter.

Collection of Computer Data

When you visit the Styletread website, whether as an account holder or a visitor, our servers and our [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html "Google Analytics") account automatically records the information that your browser captures whenever you visit a website.

This data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our site, pages of our site that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our site, access times and dates, and other statistics.

We don't treat the data collected as personal information or use it in association with other personal information, though we may aggregate, analyse and evaluate such information to better tailor or improve the services or products provided.

Identification checks

For all online purchases, you may have the chance to be randomly selected to take part in an ID check to help prevent fraudulent card and account activity.

Agreeing with the terms when purchasing, if you are randomly selected, our security team may require a screenshot or photo of your Styletread transaction as shown on your internet banking account transaction showing both the Styletread name as well as the total amount paid.

With this we can confirm that you are the account holder and no fraudulent or unauthorised activity has taken place.

Alternatively Styletread will partially refund you a small amount back into the account you made the purchase from. Once you have verified the amount we refunded it will confirm that you are the credit card holder.

Once we receive the confirmation, your order will be processed and shipped as soon as possible. If we do not receive the confirmed information within five working days your order will be cancelled and you will receive a full refund.

Address and Contact Details

Styletread Pty Ltd  
305 Gooch Street  
Thornbury VIC 3071  
Australia

email: [service@styletread.com.au](mailto:service@styletread.com.au)

ABN: 24 145 771 982 

Phone: 1300 602 947

Fax: 02 8279 9321

Last Updated: 19/02/2016
